你会魔法
So you have magic
这并没有那么棒
And it's not that great
但当它找上门的时候
But when it found you
你知道那就是命运
You know it was fate
也许现在似乎有些可怕
And it might seem scary now
但它也能很精彩
But it can be wonderful, too
那么，让我们来拥抱魔法吧
So, how about we embrace the magic
让魔法成为你的一部分
And make the magic part of you
用上一点点魔法
You take a little dash of magic
让魔法燃尽
And you let it ignite
将它们稍稍融合
Mix things up a little bit
事情会开始转好
And it might start to go right
在短短五秒之中
In just five seconds flat
故事如何改变
How the story has changed
都只是因为你已经拥抱了魔法
All cause now you've embraced the magic
一切都在变好
And it just got better in every way
我说，拥抱魔法吧
I say embrace the magic
不要再抗拒，尽情释放吧
No more holding back, just let it out
如果你能使用魔法
If you can take the magic
多了解一些魔法所能做到的
And learn a little more what it can do
一旦魔法成了你的一部分
Once the magic is part of you
阻挡你前行的障碍
What's standing in your way
有何是你当前无法破除的呢?
That you can't move today?
你拥有了内在的力量
You've got the strength in you
去实现你的梦想
To make your dreams come true
不必再闭锁你自己
No need to shield yourself
从有益的魔法
From the magic that can help
保护自己免受任何
Protect from any harm
潜在的伤害
That might come
你会魔法
So you have magic
这并没有那么棒
And it's not that great
但当它找上门的时候
But when it found you
你知道那就是命运
You know it was fate
所以，若仔细倾听
So, if you listen close
你可能会交上一个新朋友
You might make a new friend
我们齐心协力 定能成功
And together we can make it!
我说，拥抱魔法吧
I say embrace the magic
不要再抗拒，尽情释放吧
No more holding back, just let it out
如果你能使用魔法
If you can take the magic
多了解一些魔法所能做到的
And learn a little more what it can do
一旦魔法成为你的一部分
Once the magic is part of you
Once the magic is part of yoooou
一旦魔法成为你的一部分
Once the magic is part of you